# **Bhavesh Shahani**

# JAVA BACKEND DEVELOPER

Pangalore,India.

gudd.shahani@gmail.com

in BhaveshShahani\_LinkedIn

BhaveshShahani\_Github

▶ BhaveshShahani\_Portfolio



#### **EDUCATION**

## **Java Developer**

Masai School ☑ Apr 2022 – Present | Bangalore, India

## **Senior Secondary Education**

Sanmati School May 2016 | Indore

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

JAVA | SPRING BOOT | MAVEN | HIBERNATE

SQL | JAVASCRIPT | HTML | CSS | DSA

## **EXPERIENCE**

## **Store Manager**

*Mithi Mirchi Cafe* 2019 – 2020 | Indore Worked as a Store Manager.

## **Sales Manager**

*DAYA WorldWide PVT. LTD.* 2017 – 2019 | Indore Worked as a Sales Manager.

## **CERTIFICATES**

Diploma In Event Managment 🗷

JAVA Basic HackerRank 🛮

SOL Basic HackerRank 🛮

## **SOFT SKILLS**

Team Work | Problem Solving | Motivated

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Software Developer with knowledge of technologies such as Java and JavaScript. Able to learn new technologies and software. Have an experience of 1000+ hours of Coding and Data Structure Algorithms. Team player who provides valuable support in a team environment.

## **PROJECTS**

**Bus Reservation Rest\_API** 

Project Link 🛮

Rest\_API using Spring Boot.

**Tech-Stack** 

Java | SpringBoot | SQL | Hibernate | Swagger.

Responsibility

Feedback Section

\_\_\_\_\_

## Bewakoof Clone 🛮

Website 🛮

Bewakoof is a lifestyle fashion brand that makes creative, distinctive fashion for the trendy, contemporary Indian.

**Tech-Stack** 

HTML | CSS | JAVASCRIPT

Responsibility

Product Page Design | Sorting

\_\_\_\_\_

# Bath And Body Works Clone 🛮

Website ☑

Bath & Body Work is an online eCommerce cosmetic brand, Which is a retail store chain that sells soaps, lotions, fragrances, and candles.

**Tech-Stack** 

HTML | CSS | JAVASCRIPT

# Responsibility

Team Lead | Layout of the website | Merging